spiritnow.com 2011-12-31

# Spirit Now

## Prestion Media (Spirit Now) Privacy Policy

In conjunction with the Preston Media Terms of Service, which includes definitions of certain terms used herein, please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

Please be aware, this policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Preston Media does not own or control, or to people that Preston Media does not employ or manage. 

**Acceptance**

By accessing or using Preston Media or the Preston Media Network, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by and comply with this Privacy Policy, including any other posted guidelines or rules applicable to any website where the Preston Media Network is found. 

If you do not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, you are not permitted to access Preston Media or the Preston Media Network and you should exit Preston Media immediately. We're sorry to see you go. 

**General**

There are two types of information that Preston Media may collect: "Non-Personally-Identifying Information" which is information that, without additional information, cannot be directly associated with a specific person or entity; and "Personally-Identifying Information," which is information including a name, email address, phone number, etc. that, without more, can be directly associated with a specific person or entity. 

Preston Media collects personal information when you register with Preston Media, visit the Preston Media Network or the pages of certain Preston Media partners. Preston Media may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Preston Media and sign-in to our services, you are not anonymous to us; Preston Media collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. Preston Media may also ask you for credit card information to process your transactions with us, or to verify your identity or age; 

Preston Media automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the pages and products you request; Preston Media uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

You assume all responsibility for any harm or loss of privacy resulting from your voluntary disclosure of personally-identifying information. 

**Children**

Protecting children and their privacy is very important. To aid in that protection, Preston Media does not permit children under age 13 to register with Preston Media and does not knowingly maintain any personally-identifying information of children under age 13. No part of the Preston Media Network is directed to such children. If Preston Media learns that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally-identifiable information to the Preston Media Network, we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

In the event you permit a child under 13 to access the Preston Media Network in defiance of our Terms of Service, please review your responsibilities and liabilities. 

Preston Media strongly suggests that parents make use of the Parental Controls available through their Internet Provider and/or web browser to prevent unauthorized access to this site. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Preston Media does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Preston Media under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Preston Media communicate with you about offers from Preston Media and our marketing partners. However, unless you have granted permission, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information; 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Preston Media 's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law;

We will transfer information about you if Preston Media is acquired by or merged with another company. We will post a notice on our site before this occurs and/or if a new privacy policy will be applicable as a result;

Preston Media works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers. In order to bring you the products and services you have requested, we may share your personal information with them. We will not authorize these service providers to share your information other than as necessary to provide the services you have requested or beyond the extent to which you have granted us permission to do so;

and/or Preston Media may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. 

**Surveys, Contests, and Giveaways**

Preston Media may offer you the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests, giveaways and other promotions. Any information submitted in connection with such activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Emails**

By registering with Preston Media, you are agreeing to accept emails from Preston Media regarding the status of your account.Â 

All other email communication from Preston Media requires your consent to "opt-in". You have the ability to change these preferences within your account at the time of creation or at anytime thereafter, however, please allow 7-10 days for any changes to take effect. Further, emailing Preston Media directly will implicitly authorize a responsive email, which may be generated automatically. 

**Collection and Use of Information by Third Parties**

Preston Media does not permit contractors, affiliates, vendors and suppliers to disclose Personally-Identifying Information received from Preston Media, other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, third parties are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy with respect to Personally-Identifying Information that users provide directly to those third parties or that those third parties collect for themselves. 

As Preston Media is wholly independent of these third parties, this Privacy Policy does not apply to information provided to or gathered by the third parties that operate them. Before visiting a third-party website via a link on the Preston Media Network or otherwise, users should inform themselves of the privacy policies and practices, if any, of the third party responsible for that website or wireless website, and should take all steps necessary to protect their privacy. 

**Cookies, Shared Objects and Web Beacons**

Preston Media may set and access "cookies", Web Beacons or Shared Objects on your computer.   
**"Cookies"** are strings of information that a website stores on a userâ€™s computer so that the site administrator may identify your computer and passively track its activities on the website. This unique number identifies your web browser to our computer system. A cookie will not allow a website to learn any personally identifiable information (such as your real name and address) that you have not otherwise disclosed. Cookies allow us to automatically remember your web browser when you visit the Preston Media Network. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major Web sites. It is possible to adjust your Web browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is sent to your hard drive, or to refuse cookies altogether. While we do not require you to use cookies, keep in mind that the Preston Media Network may not function Properly without the aid of cookies. Therefore, users who refuse or limit cookies assume all responsibility for any loss of functionality. 

**"Shared Objects"** are used to store data on your computer in much the same way that data is stored in a cookie created through a web browser. Various uses of Shared Objects include remembering a user's favorite color, or the last frame of a movie watched. The data can only be read by movies originating from the same domain that created the Shared Object. Shared Objects cannot remember a user's e-mail address or other personal information unless they willingly provide such information. 

**"Web Beacons"** are small image files that we may place on Web pages and within certain email. Working in conjunction with cookies, Web beacons allow us to accurately count the number of unique users who have visited a specific page and the number of times those pages are displayed. We can also use Web Beacons to let us know how many people opened certain types of email. This information is only collected in aggregate form and will not be linked to your personally identifiable information. Keep in mind that any image file on a Web page can act as a Web Beacon. Third-party advertisers may use Web Beacons in their advertisements. 

Without cookies, Shared Objects and Web Beacons, it would be difficult for us to know what areas of Preston Media have a larger audience than others and give us the needed information to increase the functionality of what we do. Tracking audience size helps us to better understand when to enhance areas of the Preston Media Network and/or create and launch new services. 

Preston Media lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages or offer you products and services in connection with the Preston Media Network set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Preston Media 's cookies. 

We may use a third-party ad serving technology to help us deliver ads with some of the content you view. This technology may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visit to the website where you selected the video in order to identify and display advertisements that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving these advertisements, a unique cookie may be placed or recognized on your browser. 

**Editing and Deleting Your Account Information and Preferences**

Preston Media allows you to edit your account Information, marketing and email preferences at any time. New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. We reserve the right to send you certain communications directly to your account relating to the Preston Media Network, such as service announcements or important administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

You can terminate and delete your Preston Media account at any time. 

**Security and Confidentiality With and Within Preston Media**

Preston Media takes the security and confidentiality of information seriously and uses commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to both preserve the security and integrity of any information you transmit to Preston Media and to prevent access to personal information about you to other users and unauthorized third parties. However, this is not a guarantee, and if you chose to transmit or provide information to Preston Media you do so at your own and you are solely responsible for any losses or damages you incur as a result of any security breach. 

Further, these same commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards are utilized to ensure only those employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with your information (to provide products or services to you in order to do their jobs) are able to access your personal information, and then only to the extent necessary. 

In the event of a security breach, Preston Media will attempt to notify you electronically, including but not limited to via email or a general Preston Media Network posting, so that you may take appropriate protective measures. Depending on the laws of your state or location, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of any security breach, or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice, please notify us at: 

Preston Media, LLC  
48 West 37th Street, 7th Floor  
New York, NY 10018

**NOTICE: For important information about safe Internet usage from the Federal Trade Commission, please[click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm). (http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm) **

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Preston Media may update this policy at anytime. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Preston Media account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is set forth below. If any changes, including smaller changes, are made to this Privacy Policy you will also know because the Effective Date of the Privacy Policy will change. If Preston Media ever chooses to use any Personally Identifying Information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information was collected, we will only do so with your permission. If you do not consent, your Personally Identifying Information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time that information was obtained but you may not be able to use the Preston Media Network in the future. By using the Preston Media Network after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to the then-current privacy policy so check the Privacy Policy effective date regularly. 

**United States Residents Only**

Use of the Preston Media Network is restricted to United States residents Preston Media is located in the United States of America and is intended for use only by United States residents. If you are not a U.S. resident, you can use this site, however, you are solely responsible for making sure that your actions comply with the laws in your area. Further, you are responsible for taking any and all precautions concerning any consequences that may arise from posting Content and/or personal information for use in the United States and throughout the Internet and world. As per the Preston Media Terms of Service, the laws of the State of New York, USA, shall govern this agreement. 

Questions  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact:  
Preston Media, LLC  
48 West 37th Street, 7th Floor  
New York, NY 10018

Last update: February 21, 2008
